Abdilatif Warsame

in LinkedIn (Github

R Personal Portfolio

• 12 bay tree close, B389sh Birmingham

**** 07838192864

■ abdilatifwarsame@gmail.com

Profile

Success is my motivation, resulting in my optimistic approach to every challenge. I take every obstacle as an experience. I am a very hard worker; I push beyond my limits to gain the results I would be proud of, aiming for excellence at every task set.

Education

Full Stack Web Development,

University Of Birmingham- Coding Bootcamp 2022 – 2022 | Birmingham, United Kingdom

BA (Hons) Civil Engineering,

coventry university, Birmingham City University 2017 - 2020 | Coventry, United Kingdom

HND Combined Engineering,

Coventry University 2016 - 2017 | Coventry, United Kingdom

Languages

English

somali

arabic

Skills

React.js, Javascript, Node.js, JQuery, HTML, CSS, Express, MongoDB, MySQL, GraphQL, Agile Development, Figma

Professional Experience

customer service, IT support, sitel

2020 - 2021 | BIRMINGHAM, United Kingdom

- Responding promptly to customer inquiries.
- · Acknowledging and resolving customer complaints.
- Processing orders, forms, applications, and requests.
- Keeping records of customer interactions, transactions, comments, and complaints.
- Providing feedback on the efficiency of the customer service process.
- Ensure customer satisfaction and provide professional customer support.

Relief Security Officer, Corps Security

2019 - 2021 | BIRMINGHAM, United Kingdom At Corps, thousands of people come and go through our doors each day to work, shop, and eat. highly competent security officer tasked to monitor the premises and protect our valued staff, visitors, tenants, and inventory. trained in self-defence and first aid. Sharp eye with quick reaction time in the detection of any suspicious or criminal behaviour, and prevention of theft or vandalism.

Projects

Library Of Knowledge

live link ♂

An app that allows the user to search a curate their favourite books and even where they can buy it from.

This application was built using HTML5, CSS and JavaScript (¡Query). This webpage utilises 2 third-party APIs to render book data from a search and random inspirational quotes to give a bit of uplift to the user.

What's On - Event finder App

live link ☑

An app that allows the user to search for events in an area and invite friends to it. This application utilizes HTML, CSS, Javascript, Handlebars, Bootstrap, Google Events Web API, MySQL, Sequelize, bcrypt, Node.JS & Heroku